Charles Taylor

Principal Blockchain Engineer (Solidity / Rust / Go / WASM / Plutus)

Straightforward and competent professional with 12 years of experience as a software engineer prior to transitioning to blockchain engineering for the past 4 years. Technical lead with mindful emphasis towards security, redundancies, and decentralization for blockchain projects from conception to production.

Email:yetimonsters@gmail.comPhone:310-343-1141Linkedin:charles-taylor-302963116

github.com/fudgydrs

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Principal Blockchain Engineer (Bitus Labs), – *Irvine, CA* – Blockchain Expert and Tech Lead.

June 2022 - Current: Irvine, CA

- Go scripting and analysis
- · Solidity smart contract design, auditing, integration, and deployment
- Fintech business logic web3 and marketing
- Full stack web design (TS / JS / React / HTML / PHP / JQuery)
- MongoDB integration
- Custom API design
- API integration (Moralis / Opensea / Infura / Telegram / Twitter)
- MP4 NFT Generation (Node metadata / Python Layering & Edits)

CEO / CTO (Fudgy Labs),

- Los Angeles, CA -

Hands-on technical lead with eight subordinates: developers, artists, business manager, and marketers.

January 2019 - Current: El Segundo, CA

- Custom smart contract (Rust / Solidity / WASM / Plutus) design, integration, and deployment
- · Foundry / Hardhat Unit Testing
- Full Stack Web3 design (Websites / whitepaper / dashboards / bots)
- Unity / HTML5 Web3 implementation
- Fintech business logic web3 and marketing consultations
- Full smart contract auditing services
- · Generative NFT art services
- Paid mentorship services (including audit and CTF training)

Software Engineer (Fudgy LLC),

Los Angeles, CA –

Full Stack Software Engineer Contractor

July 2012 - March 2019: El Segundo, CA

- Blockchain backend support and A / B testing (Go / J2EE)
- C# game physics design and procedural rendering
- Reverse Auto-CAD design
- Reverse Engineer System Verilog designs
- Credit card management services
- Full Stack Web design
- C++/C/dll scripting for emulation
- Apache / ASP .NET MVC management

SKILLS

Github:

- Solidity, Rust, WASM, Plutus
- EIP Design methods
- Custom smart contracts
- React, Redux, Next, Vue,
- Java, J2EE, JQuery
- Git, Github, Gitbook, Jira, Confluence
- AWS Services (API, DB, Hosting, CI/CD
- Android, Swift, React Native, Web
- JavaScript, Typescript
- Python, Python 3
- Remix, Hardhat, Foundry
- Bots, spider, API, Arbitrage
- Infura, Moralis, NowNodes
- IPFS, Pinata, EC2 storage
- ZK (zero knowledge) proofs
- Brownie, Ganache, Waffle
- Lerna, Mocha, Cypress

EDUCATION

CSULB Grad - Dec. 2017

Bachelors of Science in Electrical Engineering with emphasis in Control Systems

Notable Projects

https://deploystarship.com

https://fractalstudios.io/

https://rektapes.co

https://omnihorse.io